import { Quiz } from '../../types';

const ColorsQuiz: Quiz[] = [
  {
    description: 'Jakou má barvu?',
    name: 'Barvy',
    questions: [
      {
        answer: ['purple'],
        question: 'fialová'
      },
      {
        answer: ['blue'],
        question: 'modrá'
      },
      {
        answer: ['red'],
        question: 'červená'
      },
      {
        answer: ['pink'],
        question: 'růžová'
      },
      {
        answer: ['orange'],
        question: 'oranžová'
      },
      {
        answer: ['yellow'],
        question: 'žlutá'
      },
      {
        answer: ['green'],
        question: 'zelená'
      },
      {
        answer: ['white'],
        question: 'bílá'
      },
      {
        answer: ['gray', 'grey'],
        question: 'šedá'
      },
      {
        answer: ['black'],
        question: 'černá'
      },
      {
        answer: ['transparent', 'clear'],
        question: 'průhledný'
      },
      {
        answer: ['light blue'],
        question: 'tyrkysová'
      },
      {
        answer: ['lilac'],
        question: 'lila'
      },
      {
        answer: ['gold'],
        question: 'zlatá'
      },
      {
        answer: ['silver'],
        question: 'stříbrná'
      },
      {
        answer: ['brown'],
        question: 'hnědá'
      }
    ]
  }
];

export default ColorsQuiz;
